<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:base="https://kindohm.com/">
    <title>Mike Hodnick&#39;s Blog</title>
    <subtitle></subtitle>
    <link href="https://kindohm.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
    <link href="https://kindohm.com/"/>
    <updated>2024-02-27T19:43:34Z</updated>
    <id>https://kindohm.com/</id>
    <author>
        <name>Mike Hodnick</name>
        <email>mike@kindohm.com</email>
    </author>
        <entry>
            <title>first</title>
            <link href="https://kindohm.com/blog/2023-02-27-first/"/>
            <updated>2023-02-27T00:00:00Z</updated>
            <id>https://kindohm.com/blog/2023-02-27-first/</id>
            <content xml:lang="en" type="html">&lt;p&gt;I&#39;m Mike. I&#39;ve been a software engineer since 1998. My
biggest interest in life is making experimental music with
electronics and computers. I also love backpacking/camping/hiking
and I try to be a better chef every day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don&#39;t know if I have much to say here on this blog, but yet
I also feel like I have a story to tell. Or maybe this&#39;ll just
be a dump for bits that I don&#39;t want to forget.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Back in the 2000&#39;s I ran my own blog that ran on .TEXT
and then &lt;a href=&quot;https://haacked.com/archive/2005/05/04/announcing-subtext.aspx/&quot;&gt;Subtext&lt;/a&gt;.
I amassed over 1000 posts on that blog but I eventually abandoned it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I currently work as a software engineer, doing a lot of React
and nodejs work. Prior to my javascript-centric life I did a
lot of .NET dev with c#. The one constant has been the web though,
and I don&#39;t really care much about what language I use as long
as I&#39;m productive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Creative coding is more fun than work coding, which is where
my musical side comes in. I compose and perform music using
the &lt;a href=&quot;https://tidalcycles.org/&quot;&gt;TidalCycles&lt;/a&gt;
livecoding environment. TidalCycles, or just &amp;quot;Tidal&amp;quot;, allows
you to sequence samples, or sequence synthesizers over MIDI.
Tidal is the end all sequencer that can do nearly anything
you can imagine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In my musical endeavors I&#39;ve been lucky to have traveled and
performed in the USA and internationally in Europe and Canada.
I&#39;ve performed at events like the Algorithmic Art Assembly
(San Francisco), Sound of Stockholm, the International
Conference on Computer Music (Limerick), Algomech (Sheffield),
among others.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not sure where this blog is going to take me. Expect anything:
a breadth of topics; posts ranging from one sentence to
many paragraphs. No idea what to expect.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
        </entry>
</feed>